Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contact Sheet 15205, circa 1967-1971
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - April 13 - ID for undeveloped roll - First three or four shots are of Pfc Edward Greth White. Story on him probably will be in a future package. Next two or three shots are of CW3 Ira C. Kirkland, for Kirkland trial story. Kirkland is white and will be only man in picture wearing a khaki uniform. All others would be in civvies or fatigues. Last shots are of a S Sgt Tucker, Negro, wearing jungle fatigues.
- Contact Sheet 15208, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Saigon nightlife.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet D - Saigon by Night - Frame 1, 2: Kids wash in gutter. 3-5: Motorcycle drivers wait for customers to take home or peddle flesh to. 7: More motorcycle drivers, etc. 8: Prostitute talks business with customer. 9-11: Tu Do street just before 12 p.m. curfew--dark and almost deserted.
- Contact Sheet 15209, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lamarr Platt (civilian) - assault - mistreatment - May/ 3 / '69 / pac.
- Contact Sheet 15210, 1969 May 31
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Richard D. Lopez - Mike Lopez - civilians / US / assault - Maj Terry Lewis - mistreatment.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #2 - Frames 8-14: (l-r) Mike Lopez, Richard Lopez. 15-18: The Flamingo Bar. 19: Maj Terris Lewis.
- Contact Sheet 15212, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Col. Sidney Gritz - officers - mistreatment - May / 3 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #4 - Only man on this roll is Gritz.
- Contact Sheet 15213, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - soldiers, fear indiv.
- Contact Sheet 15214, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy schools (diving school) - April / 19 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - March 21 - Captions for story on Navy Diving School - Sheet #5 - Art for Diving School story.
- Contact Sheet 15215, 1969 April 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - EES & commissary - man on street - April / 19 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #3: Commissary follow-up. Frame 1: Civilian shopping inside. 2-5: Almost empty commissary interior. 6: GIs and civs getting checked to see if names on list. 7, 8: More civs shopping-note full basket. 11, 12: Martinez. 14, 15: Huehner. 16, 17: White. 18, 19: Sign--US Army Commissary.
- Contact Sheet 15216, 1969 April 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - flying mission - planes (C130) - Capt. Bill Lafolette - T. Sgt. Alan Reck - Lt. Col. Eugene Jackson - April / 19 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #4 C-130 story - 2a-4a: Capt. LaFolette navigating. 5a: Cockpit during takeoff. 6a, 67: Lt Col. Jackson at work. 8a, 9a (l-r) Reck, Garrett. 10a: LaFolette. 11a: Jackson again. 12a: Reck, Garrett again. 13a: Jackson. 15a, 16a: Jackson. 17a: Pilot's eye view. 18a: Jackson. 19a: Jackson again. 20a: Chambers. 21a, 22a: Pilots at work. 23a: Chambers fiddling with controls. 24a-26a: Plane making landing-note runway approaching closer and closer in center of pix. Rest of roll--130 coming down taxiway.
- Contact Sheet 15217, 1969 April 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - flying missions - 1st Lt. John Chambers - T. Sgt. Alan Reck - planes - April / 19 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 5 - C130 story - Frames 4a, 5a: Reck taking nap during a short break. 6a, 7a: Chambers at work. 8a-16a: Changing a C130's tire. Rest of roll--plane making final approach to runways.
- Contact Sheet 15218, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - rape - Pfc. Richard D. Thomas - Pfc. Curtis Thompson - May / 3 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID shots for rape trial - Sheet B: Shots of two convicted rapists--both are circled in red in each frame of the contact sheet. Frame 2: Thompson tries to duck OW photo. Frame 3: Thomas (left) leaves courtroom after being sentenced to 10 years. Frame 5: Thompson (circled in red) ducks behind defense lawyer Berry. Frame 6: Back view of Thompson (l) and Thomas (r) as they try to duck photog. Frame 7: 2 negroes circled in red (l-r) Thompson, Thomas leave courtroom. Frame 8: (l-r) Berry, Thompson (hanging head), Thomas. Frame 9: (l-r) Berry, Thompson (hanging head), Thomas, guard. Frame 10: Circled in red (l-r) Thompson still hangs head, Thomas.
- Contact Sheet 15219, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - drinking - Sp4 Nick Dockery - Sp4 Jim Miller - Art (soldier artists) - May / 3 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - April 4 - Captions for various things - Sheet #1: Booze Ban and Combat Artists - Up to frame 11 is examples of combat artists' style of work. 12-14: Note sign banning sale of liquor. 15, 16: Inside of class six store. 17, 18: More signs--old rules versus new side by side. 19, 20: Sp4 Nick Dockery. 21, 22: Sp4 Jim Miller.
- Contact Sheet 15220, 1969 May 24
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - missions (The Shadow) - planes - sheet A & B - May / 24 / '69 / pac.
- Contact Sheet 15221, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lt. Cmdr. Jim Jetton - Da Nang Hospital - hearing story 5 / 2 / '69 - contact sheet B - story May / 24 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 2 - ID for contact sheet B - All pix are of Lt Cmdr Jim Jetton, ear, nose and throat specialist at Da Nang hospital.
- Contact Sheet 15222, 1969 May 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Vietnamese (Montagnards) / 5 / 16 / '69 - June / 14 / '69 / pac - contact sheet A + B.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 16 - ID for contact sheets A & B, Chu Kuk Montagnards - Contact Sheet A: Rest of roll: Scenes of old Montagnard hamlet from which tribespeople have moved, and women loading logs onto GI truck. Frame 7: GIs stand guard, man in civilian clothes, white shirt, no hat is Dick Alvarado, refugee adviser for Ban Me Thuot province. He's a civilian. Contact Sheet B: Scenes of new houses under construction at Chu Kuk, new tin-roofed long houses in refugee village, Montagnards inside their houses with Americans. Girl in frame 32 is OW freelancer Cynthia Copple. Frames marked with red X: Americans planning trip back to old village include Alvarado, far right, and Capt. Hal McArthur, without shirt who trains Refugee Relief Mobile Teams.
- Contact Sheet 15223, 1969 May 23
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - fraud - 1st Lt. Arthur McEnany - Capt. Tom Dugan (defense).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheet for sheet B - overseas pazifik - May 23, 69 - Frame 3: McEnany leaves courtroom after sentencing. 4, 5: McEnany (left) and defense lawyer Capt. Tom Dugan (right).
- Contact Sheet 15224, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - 1st Lt. Chuck Little - Tech. Sgt. Don Paden (getting doused) - 1st Lt. John Meiners - "bullshit bombers" - May / 17 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - April 25 - Captions for undeveloped roll #2 - This roll has the art for the story about the bullshit bombers. Guy wearing flight suit, helmet and mustache is Lt Chuck Little. Only other close-up shot on roll is Lt Meiners (Meiners does not have a mustache). The plane is 02B super sky master. Series of shots after plane is Tech Sgt Don Paden getting doused by firehose and water bucket after returning from his last psyops flight in 'Nam. After getting dunked, he's given a mug of ice-cold champagne and a plaque. Padden has more than 860 flying hours in Vietnam. He said -- "How do I feel? Great! It's about time I went home."
- Contact Sheet 15225, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Edward P. Buckley - drinking - explosives - May / 17 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - April 25 - Captions for undeveloped roll #1 - First several shots are guys carrying surfboards in the Da Nang Aerial Port. Said one--"We're lifeguards at China Beach and we're heading to Qui Nhon for course in water safety. These boards are part of equipment. Besides, I hear the surf is fine down there." Rest of roll is two frames with three people in each one, two with back to camera. One facing camera (in center of each frame) is Buckley, defendant in attempted murder trial.
- Contact Sheet 15226, 1969 May 2
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cpl. Ernesto Gomez - hero - plane crash - 5 / 2 / '69 - Gomez ammo dump - Da Nang - contact sheet A - May / 24 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 2 - ID for contact Sheet A -- Gomez and wild photos of ammo dump going up. First four frames: Cpl Ernesto Gomez standing by a CH46 helicopter. (And yes, I've told the photographer a new freelancer, to get closer to his subjects from now on.) Rest of roll: All shots of an ammunition dump which blew up in Da Nang. Fire and smoke erupt from an ammunition dump that blew up recently at the end of the Da Nang AB north-south runway. Flaming debris from a Vietnamese garbage blaze blew into grass and started a fire that spread to the ammunition. A Marine dump went up first and the holocaust spread to an Air Force dump, destroyed nearly 1,000 tons of ammo in both. Two Vietnamese civillians were killed, another 70 were hurt and an estimated 2,000 homes near the air base were destroyed. The R&R Center and Freedom Hill, a big Marine base nearby, were evacuated. The Freedom Hill PX, largest exchange in Vietnam, was destroyed.
- Contact Sheet 15227, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - clubs - US army (mess hall trouble) - May / 24 / '69 only story printed - 5th SFG - contact sheet C.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 2 - ID for Contact Sheet C - For 5th Special Forces Mess Assn. story - All pictures are of itemized list of items Aaron allegedly took out of mess assn. and hasn't paid for.
- Contact Sheet 15228, 1969 May 5
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - S. Sgt. David Tucker - 1st Lt. Joseph Dilk - AWOL - Tucker - sheet A.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption Sheet A - May 5, 69 - Sheet A - Tucker trial - Frame 3: Guy in front, wearing glasses with head circled in blue is Dilk. Color him stupid. Frame 4: Tucker and his witnesses--Tucker is 2nd from left, head circled in blue ink. 4th guy from left with head in blue ink square is Sp4 Bonie Harper, one of the men Tucker defended. Frame 5: Mug shot of Tucker.
- Contact Sheet 15229, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Art (soldier artists) - Maj. Robert L. Keeley - Pfc. Gerald Farrelly - Sp5 Adolphus Gordon - May / 3 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet D - Combat Artists - 1st Frame: S4 Hack. 2nd Frame: S5 Gordon. 3rd Frame: S5 Gordon. 4th Frame: S4 Metsche. 5th Frame: S4 Metsche. 6th Frame: PFC Farrelly. 2nd row: 1st Frame: Sign on door outside "studio" where artists work. 2nd Frame: Same as above. 3rd Frame: S4 Toothman. 4th Frame: S4 Toothman. 5th Frame: S4 Toothman. 6th Frame: S4 Hack. 3rd row: 4th Frame: (left to right, standing) Maj. Keeley, S4 Metsche, S4 Hack, PFC Farrelly (left to right kneeling) S4 Toothman, S5 Gordon. 5th and 6th frames identical arrangment as 4th.
- Contact Sheet 15230, 1969 May 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp5 Louis Salvestrini - Lt Col. Albert Busck - marriage - May / 3 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #2 art for marriage runaround story - Frames 2-4: Sp5 Salvestrini. 5-7: Sign over battalion area gate -- Zero Defects. 10, 11: Col. Busck, villain in this piece. 12, 13: Guys reading newspapers by light of full moon -- no relation to any stories in this package.
- Contact Sheet 15231, 1969 May 17
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Miss Lee (marriage broker) - marriage - May / 17 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - April 25 - ID for negatives in attached blue envelope -- Miss Lee. All are photos of Miss Lee, for flesh peddling story.
- Contact Sheet 15232, 1969 May 23
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - marriage - dependents in Vietnam - June / 6 / 1969 / O. F.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for unsouped film - May 23, 69 - The unsouped roll of Tri-x contains several shots of intertwined hands and should be used as art for the wife joins husband story. Natch they wouldn't consent to being photographed, so this will have to do. They were shot under less-than-ideal conditions, but one frame should be usable if rated at 1600 ADA and developed in Acufine. Note they don't wear wedding rings, this is part of masquerade.
- Contact Sheet 15233, 1969 June 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Crimes - Plat Sgt Roy E. Bumgarner - June / 14 / '69 / pac - used June 14, issue Bumgarna.
- Contact Sheet 15234, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - marriage - Julie Quillen - Gary Quillen - contact sheet A Julie 5 / 23 / '69 - June / 14 / '69 / pac.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 22 - ID for contact sheet A - For story of Julie - Frames 1-4: Gary, son of Julie and Sgt Lloyd D. Quillen. Frames 5-8: Julie.
- Contact Sheet 15267, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - shooting.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 12 - ID for Contact sheets A & B, all for Rodriquez trial - Sheet A: First six frames: Television reporters interview Mrs. Willette when she arrives in Saigon to attend trial of her son's killer. Next four frames: Mrs. Willette and Bernardo Rodriquez Sr., father of the accused man, (wearing civilian clothes and hat) outside courtroom at Cu Chi. Rest of roll: Shots outside the courtroom, with Mrs. Willette in most of them. She's wearing a big "Women for Peace" button.
- Contact Sheet 15268, 1969 June 7
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet B - First five frames: Buddies hustle Rodriquez out of courtroom, shielding him from cameras, and into waiting jeep. His father and Mrs. W. are in the third frame, as she tries to talk with Sgt Rodriquez. Last six frames: Mrs. Willette talks with Pfc Jeffrey Clark, of the 25th MP Co at Cu Chi, after the trial. Clark was a friend of her son's, and he was the only soldier she was able to talk to, except for JAG officials. Undeveloped roll of film: All are shots of a picture of Asa Martin Jr., included a pencil note he'd clipped to the photo saying "Will be home very soon, Love, Junior."
- Contact Sheet 15269, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - taxi - May / 3 / '69 (pictures not printed).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - April 25 - Saigon cabbies.
- Contact Sheet 15270, 1969 May 26
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lt. Col. Bernard Matthey - Laundry.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet - May 26, 69 - Hirst - Sheet #1-125th Sig Bn gripe story - Frames 4-6: Guys stomp on their own wet laundry, in old fashioned washing technique, since maids were fired. 7-8: View from inside to outside from where air conditioner used to be. 9-11: Guy points to spot where conexes are buried. (don't use frame 9 because somebody might recognize rather distinctive watchband on guy's left hand.) 12-14: Ltc Matthey.
- Contact Sheet 15271, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - awards - Col. Paul Tobin - Col. Robert Ivey.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pazifik - May 30 - Photo ID for contact Sheet A - Tobin story - Frames 11-14: Colonel Robert H. Ivey, MacV staff judge advocate (left), presented Legion of Merit to Col. Paul Tobin (center), law officer, a few days before Tobin left Vietnam. Cut out man on right--don't know his name. 16: Tobin. 17-19: Ivey, left, Tobin, right. 20: Tobin. 21: Ivey, left, Tobin, right.
- Contact Sheet 15272, 1969 June 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Tony Martin.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Captions for sheets 1-4 - June 8, 69 - Sheet #1: Tony Martin story--entire roll shots of Tony doing his thing at the Saigon USO. All shots self-explanatory.
- Contact Sheet 15278, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Marines - patrol mission - Sgt. Pedro M. Padilla - Lance Cpl. Randy K. Pool - Pfc. Ronald T. Graebel - Pfc. Kenneth M. Matesic.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - June 2 - ID for negative holder marked A - pictures for recon patrol story by Dennis Rutherford - Frame 23A: Sgt Pedro M. Padilla, the team leader, looks through field glasses. Frame 24A: L Cpl Randy K. Pool eats can of C rations during break on second day of mission. Frame 16A: Pfc Ronald T. Graebel making way through jungle. Frame 17A: Pfc Kenneth M. Matesic thinks he hears suspicious noises in jungle. Frame 19A: PFC Kenneth M. Matesic rests during a break. Frame 0A: Team waits in CH46 helicopter before insertion on mission. Frame 12A: L Cpl Pool talks on radio while HN Floyd J. Moore keeps watch. Frame 23: Sgt Padilla during the fight. Pic taken just before he was wounded by a hand grenade.
- Contact Sheet 15279, 1969 June 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - Sp4 Harold Armwood (accident) - 1st Lt. David T. Morgan - 1st Sgt. James G. Weinburg - Lt. Col. Royce Powell - Capt. Edward C. Bierma.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - ID for Armwood murder trial--June 8, 1969 - Contact Sheet A - Frame 9: 1st Lt. David T. Morgan--defense witness. Frame 10: 1st Sgt James G. Weinburg--defense witness. Frame 11: Ltc Royce Powell--defense witness. Frame 12: Sp4 Harold Armwood--the accused. Frame 13: (left to right) Capt. Edward C. Bierma, Defense Counsel, 1st Sgt Weinburg, Sp4 Armwood, 1st Lt. Morgan.
- Contact Sheet 15280, 1969 May 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Marines - Pfc. Larry Johnson - Pfc. Eugene Morse - 2nd Lt. Patrick Normanly - Lance Corp. Robert ?? - Pfc. Richard Muller - Capt. John Palchak.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet - May 19, 69 - Hirst - Sheet 1: Marine combat stories. Frames 11-14: Pfc Larry Johnson and captured pistol. 15, 16: Pfc Eugene Morse wearing flak jacket like the one that saved 1/2 his life. 17, 18: 2d Lt Patrick Normanly. 19, 20: L Cpl Robert McMullin. 19, 20: Pfc Richard Muller holds pen inside bullet hole in canteen. 21, 22: Capt John Palchak.
- Contact Sheet 15281, 1969 May 16
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Jimmy C. Halpain (June / 7 / '69) - Sp4 Dale Thompson (June / 21 / '69) - contact sheet C (5 / 16 / '69) - Halpain & Thompson trials.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazifik - May 16 - ID for Halpain Court Martial and Thompson Court Martial - Frames A & 1: Sp4 Jimmy C. Halpain--used June 14. Frame 2: Sp4 Dale Thompson.
- Contact Sheet 15284, 1969 June 21
  Contact sheet containing 40 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Entertainment (Rainbow Club in Nha Trang) - leave towns.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo Captions for "Ants" Photo Neg Set Number 2 - Row 2-6: (nearest to cardboard) Singer with hips is Annie. Row 3A-7: Picture 3A and 4A, the Ants sitting on the porch rail of the Rainbow Club in Nha Trang before show time. From L to R: Dan, Truc, John, Mai and Ellen. Picture 5A: Mai. 6A: Dan, John, Mai, Truc. Row 7A-12A: 7A, 8A, 9A: Dan, John, Mai, Truc. 10A: John, Ellen, Truc. 11A: Ellen, Truc. 12A: Dan, Ellen, Truc, Mai. Row 13A-18A: 13A & 14A, Ellen in fore, Truc in back. 15A: Dan, Ellen, Truc, Mai. 16A, 17A: Same as above. 18A: Dan, Mai, John, Truc, seen over GI shoulders. 19A-23A: Mai singing, seen over GI shoulders. Row 25A-30A: 25A-28A: Ellen Singing. 29A: Ellen and John. 30A: Dan and Ellen (John in back). Row 31A-36A: 31A: Dan, Ellen, John. 32A: Ellen, John. 33A-36A: Ellen dancing in fore, John and Truc in back.
- Contact Sheet 15285, 1969 June 21
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - mission schools (Recondo).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Recondo School, Mike Force, STABO - Identifications - May 8, 1969 - Frames A, 1, 2, 3, 4: Students looking at result of ambush set up by instructors. Ambush was made with explosives tied to Det cord, cord placed in a 100 ft. diameter circle, set off by blasting cap. On Hon Tre Island, Recondo School. Frame 6: Student standing by cardboard replica of a man in middle of ambush. Holes in replica where shrapnel hit. Man would be dead in real ambush. Frame 7: Students searching ambush area. Frame 8: Tiger-fatigued Recondo students march up hill on Hon Tre Island after looking at ambush. Frame 9: Instructers campt on Hon Tre Island. Goofing off. Frames 10 & 11: Chopper lands on Hon Tre. Frames 12 to 18: Mike Force quick reaction (with long cutline). Frames 24A to end: Phillip Ahumada. Demonstration STABO (For STABO story).
- Contact Sheet 15288, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - mission schools (Recondo), 1969 06 21
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pazific - May 9 - Recondo School & STABO - Frames A & 1: Chopper landing at Hon Tre Island--training grounds for MACV Recondo School. Frames 2 & 3: Instructor talking to visitors to Hon Tre. Frames 4 & 5: Instructors camp at Hon Tre. Frame 6: Terrain of Hon Tre Island. Frame 8: Teams of students just back from field exercise relax for a minute before next instruction. Frames 11 & 12: One team of students interviewed, L to R, Sgt Charles Hinton, Sgt Norman Crabb, Sgt Ray Harvell, Sp4 Billy Faulks, Sp4 Rob Wallace. Frames 13 & 14: An student at Recondo School who fell out of a McGuire Rig 120 feet up, sprained wrist. Frames 15 to 20: Instructor on Hon Tre Island teaching class about use of explosives for ambushes. Frame 22: Landscape of Hon Tre Island.
- Contact Sheet 15290, 1969 July 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - rape - acquittal - Sgt. Albert Jones - Pfc. Walt DeCastro - Tran Thi Hiep ("victim") - Sp4 Lance Baker.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: The subject of this film is the victim of the rape (they were acquitted) and her name is Tran Thi Hiep. The old man squatting down beside her is her father and his name is Tran Le. They are pictured waiting outside the courtroom before testifying.
- Contact Sheet 15291, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - rape - acquittal - Sgt. Albert Jones - Pfc. Wade DeCastro - Sp4 Lance Baker.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: The contents of this film refer to the rape trial acquittal story included in this package. The subject here is the three defendents whose names we are not using. However in the caption you may refer to them as Jones, Baker, DeCastro as those are the name we gave them in the story (all explained in an editors note).
- Contact Sheet 15292, 1969 July 12
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - currency (bogus money orders).
- Contact Sheet 15293, 1969 July 19
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - love & sex - Helen & Janie.
- Contact Sheet 15294, 1969 July 12
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - recreation - planes - Capt. George W. Caulkett - Carol young husband - Suda Prohaska.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: IDs for R&R airline story - Frame #3: A local cutie of the the Pan Am offices at Tan Son Nhut airport greets returning R& R passengers to guide them through customs and immigration. 4: R&R GIs return to the war, disembark from plane. 5: Girl from the local Pan Am office. 6: More disembarking GIs. 7, 8, & 9: Pan Am hostess Suda Prohaska says goodbye to her passengers as they leave the plane to head back to the war. 10, 11, 12, 13: Four steward from the Pan Am R&R flight: L to R -- Carol Younghusband of Tiburon, California; Shirley Fukuda of San Mateo, California; Suda Prohaska of Belmont, California; Andrea Jackson of Sausalito, California. 14, 15: Captain George W. Caulkett of Kentfield, California sits in the cockpit as he prepares to crank up the engines. 16: GI's loading on the big 707. 17: Hostess Shirley Fukuda greets greets her front-cabin passengers at the door. 18, 19, 20: Hostess Shirley Fukuda checks out her passengers before takeoff.
- Contact Sheet 15295, 1969 June 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - mail - currency - Pvt. Robert Weder - Pvt. Larry Dedmon - Capt. Jay Siegel - Douglas Pravitz.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID for Pravitz Court Martial - June 30 1969 - Frame 4 & 5: Pvt Robt. Weder. Frame 6 & 7: Pvt Larry Dedmon. Frame 8 & 9: Capt. Jay Seigel. Frame 10, 11, 12: Sp4 Pravitz (left) and his father, Douglas Pravitz.
- Contact Sheet 15296, 1969 June 6
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - officers - Air Force - flying missions - Capt. Benny Blick - Capt. Jim Coffman.